{
  "chapter": 18,
  "data": [
    {
      "question": "Portability enables the components to",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Communicate with other components",
        "Move in other environments",
        "Become light weight",
        "None of these"
      ],
      "answer": 2
    },
    {
      "question": "The interoperability is not applicable on which of the following?",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Application",
        "Application platform",
        "Data",
        "None of these"
      ],
      "answer": 2
    },
    {
      "question": "Portability and interoperability can be achieved by standardizing the format(s) of",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "APIs",
        "Data",
        "Communication protocols",
        "All of these"
      ],
      "answer": 4
    },
    {
      "question": "Tell if the statement is ‘true’ or ‘false’. ‘IaaS stores raw data files. Portability is not applicable on the IaaS level data.’",
      "incorrect_answers": ["True", "False"],
      "answer": 2
    },
    {
      "question": "Machine imaging helps in",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Hardening security of VM",
        "recovering easier disaster Deploying of VM easily",
        "Both a and b"
      ],
      "answer": 2
    },
    {
      "question": "JeOS is a part of",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Virtual appliance",
        "Machine image",
        "Both a and b",
        "None of these"
      ],
      "answer": 1
    },
    {
      "question": "Virtual appliance is one kind of software appliance. This statement is",
      "incorrect_answers": ["True", "False"],
      "answer": 1
    },
    {
      "question": "Virtual appliances are useful because they provide",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "More security",
        "Ease of installation",
        "Liberty from complex configuration",
        "All of these"
      ],
      "answer": 4
    },
    {
      "question": "Each virtual appliance is generally made to distribute",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "One single application",
        "At least two applications",
        "Any number of applications",
        "None of these"
      ],
      "answer": 1
    },
    {
      "question": "Virtual appliances are distributed in which of these common packaging formats?",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Open virtual format",
        "Open volatile format",
        "Open virtualization format",
        "None of these"
      ],
      "answer": 3
    },
    {
      "question": "OVF descriptor that contains metadata related to the OVF package is a",
      "incorrect_answers": ["OVF file", "XML file", "VMDK file", "HTML file"],
      "answer": 2
    },
    {
      "question": "Formats of virtual disk images created by different machine virtualization vendors are",
      "incorrect_answers": ["Same", "Different"],
      "answer": 2
    },
    {
      "question": "Which server virtualization vendor uses VMDK as format for capturing virtual disk images?",
      "incorrect_answers": ["Oracle", "Microsoft", "Google", "VMware"],
      "answer": 4
    },
    {
      "question": "The OVA (Open Virtualization Appliance) format for supplying OVF package in a single archive file is a",
      "incorrect_answers": ["Zip file", "Tar file", "Rar file", "Zipx file"],
      "answer": 2
    },
    {
      "question": "Use of some standard and common APIs by all cloud service vendors will increase",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Application portability",
        "Application standard",
        "Cost benefits of business",
        "All of these"
      ],
      "answer": 4
    },
    {
      "question": "The development of Open-source Simple Cloud API to improve portability of cloud applications was an initiative taken by",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Rackspace",
        "Distributed Management Task Force (DMTF)",
        "Cloud Security Alliance",
        "Zend Technologies "
      ],
      "answer": 4
    },
    {
      "question": "The Simple Cloud API was developed to improve portability",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "PHP applications",
        "Java applications",
        "Cloud applications",
        "All applications"
      ],
      "answer": 1
    },
    {
      "question": "Bundling virtual appliance in OVF package format helps",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "To harden the security of VM",
        "To increase application portability",
        "To increase portability of platform",
        "To market them easily"
      ],
      "answer": 2
    },
    {
      "question": "Which among the following organizations works towards promotion of interoperable standards for cloud applications?",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "VMware",
        "Distributed Management Task Force (DMTF)",
        "Citrix",
        "Cloud Security Alliance"
      ],
      "answer": 2
    },
    {
      "question": "The data, application or platform portability problems faced in cloud environment.",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "It was not there in traditional environment",
        "It is an unique problem for cloud",
        "It was there in traditional environment also",
        "The platform portability problem is new to cloud."
      ],
      "answer": 3
    }
  ]
}
